Michiko Zafe

Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

Citi (Citigroup Business Processing Solutions), BGC, Taguig

Customer Solutions Officer

APRIL 2013 - FEBRUARY 2016

Assists US Credit Card clients with their billing and account online concerns. Responsible for ensuring that all client's concerns are resolved to their satisfaction.

 $\label{lem:promotes} Promotes \ financial \ solutions \ to \ clients \ like \ balance \ transfers \ and \ card \ conversions.$

Teletech Customer Care Management, Quezon City

Customer Service Representative 1

MARCH 2012 - JANUARY 2013

Handles Savings/Checking Account concerns from US Clients.

Assists clients with their Account Online concerns

Convergys Philippines, Quezon City

Sales and Service Representative

DECEMBER 2010 - DECEMBER 2011

Assists AT&T clients with their cell phone concerns including both technical and billing. Responsible for completing sales order from clients.

Manages payments and other billing concerns.

Caritas Health Shield Inc., Pasig City

Administrative Officer/Customer Service

MARCH 2006 – MAY 2007

Processes health card applications of new clients

EDUCATION

ZUITT Coding Bootcamp, Makati City

Full-Stack Web Development

MARCH 2019 - JUNE 2019

Our Lady of Fatima University, Quezon City

Bachelor of Science in Nursing

MARCH 2010

C30-1L, The Cambridge Village Condominium, San Andres, Cainta, Rizal

(+63) 9177648844 michiko.silvestre@yahoo.com

PROFILE

Creative and dependable web developer with experience in building rich, responsive and interactive web applications.

SKILLS

Programming Language:Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, PHP

Frameworks: Node JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, Express, React, Laravel

Others: SASS, GIT, MySQL, MongoDB, Heroku, JWT, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere, After Effects

LANGUAGES

English, Filipino

PORTFOLIO

https://michikozafe.netlify.com